(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-04T22:48:05.522974",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration now open!
ローソンにお越しの皆さん！
To everyone visiting Lawson!
2026年3月
March 2026...
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
Lawson campaign confirmed!
今回はこの6人が登場！
Featuring these 6 members this time!
詳細は3月9日(月)公開予定！
Details to be revealed on Monday, March 9!
今年のバンダイブースも激アツ！
This year's Bandai booth is super exciting too!
注目のおすすめ商品を初公開！
Unveiling recommended hot products for the first time!
会場限定 スペシャルフォトブース！
Venue-exclusive special photo booth!
あなただけのカードデザイン！
Your very own custom card design!
限定カードももらえる！
You can also get exclusive cards!
特設サイトで情報公開中！
Information now available on the special site!
みるハコ
Miruhako
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams JOYSOUND みるハコで配信決定!!
[hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams - Streaming confirmed on JOYSOUND Miruhako!!]
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over...
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Now, let's hop aboard!
Ridin' on Dreams Yeah!!
Wow oh oh... Hey!! Hey!! Yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a small dream,
想像できないような
feelings grew beyond...
想いになったんだ
anything I could have imagined.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
our bond becomes our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can just blow it all away!
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey,
漕いでる途中に
as we row along right now,
困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be hardships too.
それも力に変えて
Turning even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
we'll move forward together!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves.
“らしさ”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining as myself!
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you...
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, is my greatest treasure,
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
so holding hands and cheering each other on,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going on and on!
Ridin' on Dreams
Wow oh oh... Hey!! Hey!! Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind tries to confuse...
行く先乱そうとも
the direction where we are heading,
あの日誓ったんだ
we made a vow on that day,
覚悟は揺るがない
our determination will never waver!
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Pushing us forward, saying "I gotta pull myself together!"
明日への橋になる
it becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to treasure this even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どっから始めたらいいかもがいて
struggling to figure out where to begin,
少しずつね 輪になって見つけた
bit by bit, gathering in a circle, we found...
何にも代えられない夢だ
an irreplaceable dream!
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even what is incomplete,
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
our feelings are as one.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
わずかな希望でも
Even if it's just a tiny glimmer of hope,
僕と君でずっと
together with you, forever,
馬鹿にされても
even if others make fun of us,
信じたい！
I want to believe!
ねぇ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough...
ねぇ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing...
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねぇ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves.
“らしさ”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining as myself!
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you...
ねぇ、宝物だから
Hey, is my greatest treasure,
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
so holding hands and cheering each other on,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行けるから！
we can still keep going on!
ひとりじゃない
You are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Standing up as many times as it takes,
笑い合っていたい
I want us to keep smiling together!
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
Sharing our wishes together, come on!
手を繋いで 想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going on and on!
Ridin' on Dreams
Wow oh oh... Hey!! Hey!! Yeah!!
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Notice: To All Visitors]
hololive Dreams 事前登録受付中！
[hololive Dreams: Pre-registration Open!]
宝鐘海賊団
[Banner] Houshou Pirate Crew
あじまる
[Text on phone] Ajimaru
これが星街再演 サインぬい!!!!!!
[Text on phone] This is the Suisei rerun signed plushie!!!!!!
ローチケ当たったので... 解散かも？
[Text on phone] I won the Lawson ticket... maybe disband?
声出せ!! Make some noise!!
[Text on tablet] Make some noise!!
あしたは月曜日
[Text on tablet] Tomorrow is Monday
マリン船長 400万人 おめでとう
[Sign] Congrats to Captain Marine on 4 million!
Fxxkin ローソンチケット 落選
残念ながら今回はチケットをご用意することができませんでした
[Text on shirt] Fxxkin Lawson Ticket: Unsuccessful
Unfortunately, we were unable to secure a ticket for you.
今日も天才
[Sign] Genius today as well
声出しして行く
[Text on phone] Time to make some noise
森カリオペ推し！
[Towel] Mori Calliope Fan!
あしたは月曜日
[Sign] Tomorrow is Monday
シルベ最高
[Text on phone] Silver is the best
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams]
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉 届けて
Layering our words into harmony, let them reach you!
Yeah!
たどたどしく描いては いじけないと笑ってた
Fumbling as we drew our dreams, we laughed, saying we wouldn't shrink back.
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
Predicting the future, let's see the continuation of that day.
手と手繋いで 風も着こなしていこう
Hand in hand, let's embrace the wind as we go.
広がる世界へ 連れて行くよ
I'll take you to an expanding world.
どんなときもきっと 一緒なら叶えられる
Whenever it is, if we're together, we can make it come true.
La la la la... 止まない 希望のベル ほら
La la la la... look, the endless bell of hope!
La la la la... 聞こえてる？ 歌声
La la la la... can you hear it? The singing voice.
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Layering our words into harmony,
鮮やかな 日々の向こう
beyond those vivid days,
いつも君と 導くよ
I will always guide you.
ストーリー 心に 結んだ夢が
A story, the dream bound in our hearts,
揃え 駆けてゆく
aligning together as we run forward.
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ
Riding on the sparkle to reach you,
届け メロディー どこまでも
reach out, melody, wherever you go!
何気ない言葉を交わして
Exchanging casual words,
一人じゃないよって深呼吸
I take a deep breath knowing I'm not alone.
痛くて楽しい魔法の言葉
Magical words that are painful yet fun.
ひと息ついて 遠く見据えて
Catching a breath and gazing far ahead,
また君を知って この旅に
getting to know you again on this journey,
ちょっと勇気出していこう 明日へ飛んでいけ
let's gather a little courage and fly toward tomorrow!
La la la la... 導く 道標は
La la la la... the guiding signpost,
まだ まだ まだ 覚えている 歌声
is the singing voice I still, still, still remember.
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら 足元に 虹がかかる
If we reach our hands out into harmony, a rainbow forms under our feet.
君と跳ねる 弾む ステージ
Bouncing and jumping on stage with you.
ハーモニー 記した場所へ 運ぶ 約束を 輝きに乗せて
Harmony takes our promise to the marked place, riding on the shine.
世界へ
To the world,
響け
resound!
メロディ いつまでも
May this melody last forever.
君と踏み出したあの日 あの瞬間が
That day, that moment when I took a step forward with you,
宝物だって胸を張る 今
I can now proudly say is a true treasure.
歩いて 話して はしゃいで 笑っていくんだ
Walking, talking, having fun, and laughing together,
色褪せないまま
without ever fading away.
混ざり合う 僕らの声 ほら
Our voices blend together, look,
聞こえてる みんな
everyone can hear them!
ハーモニー 重ねた過去が 鮮やかな 日々の向こう
Harmony—our accumulated past lies beyond those vivid days.
君と (君と) 描く新しいストーリー
A new story painted with you (with you).
ハーモニー 結んだ夢が 空へ 駆けていく 煌めきに乗せて
Harmony—our tied dreams run toward the sky, riding on sparkles.
あなたへ
To you,
世界へ
to the world,
響け
resound,
愛を
our love!
メロディ どこまでも
May this melody reach everywhere.
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! We're gonna shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
Guided by our calling voices!
Parade, Parade, Parade! 探しに行く
Parade, Parade, Parade! We'll go searching!
スタートは何度だって
We can start over as many times as it takes!
ただ 独り言を綴った
I just jotted down soliloquies,
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I just ran because I wanted to begin.
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Far off, lit up in the darkness,
それは 眩しすぎた名前
was a name that shone far too brightly.
それは 優しすぎる思い出もっと
Memories that are far too gentle,
近づけと手を伸ばした
telling me to come closer as I reached out my hand.
思いがけず結び合った
We unexpectedly connected with each other.
ほら 今
Look, right now,
迷子は
the lost ones
“僕等”になった
have become "us."
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along both your regrets and your love.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは 光
Our modest prayers become light.
終わりなき兆し
An endless sign.
君を見つけたこと
Having found you,
胸を張れるよ
I can stand proud.
ここから
From here,
これから
from now on,
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
まだ 頼りない予感を
Still holding onto an uncertain hunch,
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
let's sing out, there's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けない イマジナリー
An imaginary world that no one can unravel,
いつか また逢えるおまじない
a spell to ensure we'll meet again someday.
あの日 ゼロに始まった ストーリー
The story that started from zero that day,
数え切れない言葉
countless words,
数えるような想いじゃないさ
feelings that can't simply be counted up.
ほら 今
Look, right now,
“僕等”を
let me call
一つと呼ぼう
all of us "one."
Parade, Parade, Parade! 美しいんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It's so beautiful!
許し合える刹那
In this instant of mutual forgiveness,
夜は きらめく
the night glimmers.
Parade, Parade, Parade! 跨いだ大空
Parade, Parade, Parade! Striding across the vast sky,
相応しい旅路と
a journey truly fitting...
君と歩くことが
Walking alongside you...
君と在ることなんだ
Is what it means to be with you.
「ただいま」を聞けば
When I hear "I'm home,"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I shout back "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that natural?
parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine!
暗がりを満たすのは
What fills the darkness...
君だ 僕だ！
Is you, and me!
parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along both your regrets and your love,
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer becomes a light,
終わりなき兆し
An endless sign of what's to come.
君と飛び込んでゆく
We'll dive right in with you,
素敵なスタートさ
A wonderful start!
ここから これから
From here, from now on!
Our Bright Parade, parade!
プロデュースステージ、スタートです！
Produce stage, start!
WHAT'S UP 1, 1, 1! 騒いでいくよ！
WHAT'S UP 1, 1, 1! Let's get loud!
言葉を彩れ！
Color your words!
全開の夜へ！
Into a night at full power!
hololive 4th fes. 最後のステージだ！
hololive 4th fes., it's the final stage!
風に吹かれて 誰にも気づかれぬよう
Blown by the wind, so no one notices,
区別がつかない モノクロの世界
In an indistinguishable monochrome world.
色を足しても 何も見えなくて
Even if I add color, I still can't see anything,
まるで私は 息を止めていた
It's as if I had been holding my breath.
もういいよ
It's alright now.
遠くても叶えたい 私は
Even if it's far away, I want to make it come true,
こんな世界 想いも抱きしめていたいのに
Even though I want to embrace my feelings in a world like this.
夢のキャンバスに居続ける意味は
The meaning of staying on this canvas of dreams
この胸に輝いているストーリー
Is the story shining inside my heart.
触れ合えない言葉
Words that can never touch,
揺れる意識の限界
The limit of a wavering consciousness.
それぞれの夜は 響き合う機会
Each of our nights is a chance to resonate,
散らかった時に 果て
At the end of scattered time,
また紐解けるのかな
Will we be able to unravel it again?
疑問の中のフィードバック
Feedback amidst doubts,
誰もいなく埋まった道を歩いている
I walk down a deserted, buried path.
迷い蠢く
Wriggling in confusion,
重ねてゆくおとぎ話の正体
The true nature of accumulating fairy tales.
くもりなき空の
Under a cloudless sky,
心が持つ熱を
The heat held within my heart,
憧れを照らす
Illuminates my longing.
風に吹かれて
Blown by the wind,
思い出してしまうのに
Even though I end up remembering,
ごまかしてしまうのは
The reason I keep glossing it over
音の波になった後悔から
Is from the regret that became waves of sound.
ああ 月明かりの夜は
Ah, on a moonlight night,
さよならを知らせるバニッシュよ
A vanish that signals farewell.
光を繋ぐ旅ゆく風のように
Like the traveling wind connecting lights.
歩んできた道のりは今も
The path I've walked is still here,
いずれ後悔してしまう日が来ても
Even if a day comes when I regret it,
私はまだ終わらない
I am far from finished.
空に浮かぶ月の光を
Looking up at the moonlight floating in the sky...
好きよ
I love you...
怒りに触れるたび強くなってしまうの
Every time I touch anger, I end up growing stronger.
それが LOVE
That is LOVE.
染まってしまおう
Let's get completely dyed in it.
どれも愛を模した TRUE
Each one is TRUE, modeled after love.
はーい！皆様！
Hi, everyone!
この度は私、愛しの旦那様へ...
Today, to my beloved husband...
今すぐ抱きしめてチュッチュッチュッでございますよ！
Hug me right now with a kiss, kiss, kiss!
待っててね！ダーリン！もう破滅しちゃう！
Wait for me, darling! I'm gonna fall completely apart!
抑えきれないの
I can't hold it back.
私のハートがぐちゅぐちゅしてる
My heart is squishing all around.
澄まない瞳
Clear eyes,
咎める唇
reproachful lips,
無邪気な笑顔
an innocent smile...
もう止まらないの
I can't stop anymore!
私の中の何かがドゥドゥドゥドゥギャー！
Something inside of me goes dudududu gyaa!
溢れ出しちゃう
It's overflowing!
頭の先までビンビン感じちゃう
I feel it tingling all the way to the top of my head!
愛おしい愛おしい子猫ちゃん
My sweet, sweet little kitten,
隠れてないで顔見せて
don't hide, show me your face!
風邪と私病気の
The percentage of cold and my sickness...
パーセンテージ 出力最大！
Maximum output!
見ーつけた！
Found you!
胸がキュンキュン
My heart goes flutter flutter!
愛は止まらないの 好き好き大好き 好き好き Kiss me
Love won't stop! Love you, love you, love you so much, love you, love you, kiss me!
私だけのお姫様 もう離さないずっと
My very own princess, I won't ever let you go!
教会で挙式をあげましょう
Let's hold our wedding at the church!
神様だって断れない
Even God can't refuse!
思い立ったので行っちゃおう ハネムーン
Since the idea struck me, let's go on our honeymoon!
ガチでお嫁においでチュッ！
Seriously, become my bride, mwah!
ただいま！ダーリン！お帰りなさいのチュ〜は？
I'm home, darling! Where's my welcome-home kiss?
さて、ご飯にしようかな？お風呂にしようかな？それとも...
Now then, should I make dinner? Or prepare a bath? Or maybe...
今日はこれから二人で楽しいショッピングデート！ダーリン、もう準備出来てる？
Today we're going on a fun shopping date together! Darling, are you ready yet?
ダーリン？どこにいるの？
Darling? Where are you?
もしかして、沙花叉とかくれんぼしたいのかな？
Could it be you want to play hide-and-seek with Sakamata?
テーブルの下？クローゼットの中かな？
Under the table? Or inside the closet?
よし！沙花叉、本気出しちゃうぞ〜！出力最大！
Alright! Sakamata's gonna get serious! Maximum output!
甘い言葉を織りなす
Weaving sweet words,
赤い糸で二人繋がっているの
the two of us are connected by a red thread.
ハートがビンビン来てるよ Baby
My heart is tingling so hard, baby!
見ーつけた！
Found you!
恋はもう誰にも止められないの
Nobody can stop this love anymore!
好き好き大好き 好き好き Kiss me
Love you, love you, love you so much, love you, love you, kiss me!
私だけの愛の姿 もう逃がさないずっと
My very own embodiment of love, I won't ever let you escape!
永遠の愛を誓いましょう
Let's swear our eternal love!
神様だってサイン給わるよ
Even God will sign off on this!
我慢できない 早起きしちゃおう
I can't hold back, let me wake up early!
Go to heaven
檻の中に
Inside a cage,
囚われて 孤立いつでも It's my love
trapped and isolated, always... It's my love!
病めるときも 健やかなるときも 命ある限り ラブラブチュッチュすることを誓います！
In sickness and in health, for as long as I live, I swear to stay madly in love and kiss, kiss!
世界で一番愛してるよ
I love you more than anyone in the whole world.
Baby もう私を一人にしないで
Baby, don't leave me alone anymore!
あなたがいないとダメなの 寂しがり屋な私
I can't survive without you, I get so lonely...
あなたのそばに居させてずっと
Let me stay by your side forever and ever!
皆様も愛してるよー！
I love all of you too~!
胸がキュンキュン 愛は止まらないの 好き好き大好き 好き好き Kiss me
My heart goes flutter flutter, love won't stop! Love you, love you, love you so much, love you, love you, kiss me!
私だけのお姫様 もう離さないずっと
My very own princess, I won't ever let you go!
教会で挙式をあげましょう
Let's hold our wedding at the church!
神様だって全否定できない
Even God can't completely deny us!
思い立ったので行っちゃおう ハネムーン
Since the idea struck me, let's go on our honeymoon!
お嫁においでチュッ！
Become my bride, mwah!
ありがとう！ダーリン！
Thank you, darling!
チュッ！
Mwah!
あ～！マリンちゃんがめっちゃ好き～！
Ah! I love Marine-chan so much~!
ないない足りないないない
Not enough, not enough, not not enough
ないない船がないない
No ship, no ship, there's no ship
背に腹替えられない
Desperate times call for desperate measures
マニが終わった
My money is all gone!
円 ドル ポンド ユーロ Money しゅきしゅき！ Ah!
Yen, dollar, pound, euro, money, love it, love it! Ah!
ルピア リラ ウォン 元 ドン！ Money Money Money！
Rupiah, lira, won, yuan, dong! Money, money, money!
はい！寄ってらっしゃい買ったら
Yes! Step right up, buy it!
おいでの社長様
Welcome, dear CEO!
お宝売りますわ
I'll sell you some treasures!
Let's オークション！
Let's auction!
髑髏の旗！
Skull flag!
オンボロパーカー！
Tattered hoodie!
リップに眼帯は？
Lipstick and an eyepatch?
しあわせに How much? (はい！100万円！)
How much for happiness? (Yes! 1 million yen!)
からの？ (はい！1億円！)
And then? (Yes! 100 million yen!)
からの？ (はい！1兆円！)
And then? (Yes! 1 trillion yen!)
増した声 How much?
A louder voice, How much?
(はい！1千兆！) からの？
(Yes! 1 quadrillion!) And then?
(はい！2千兆！) からの？
(Yes! 2 quadrillion!) And then?
(はい！3千兆！) ぶっ飛んで？
(Yes! 3 quadrillion!) Go crazy?
(5千兆！) 欲しいの欲しいの Money Money
(5 quadrillion!) I want it, I want it, Money Money
助けて欲しいの Give me! Give me!
Help me out, Give me! Give me!
脱出 Horny Money Bar
Escape the Horny Money Bar
Pare Pare Pare Pare Pare Pirate
売り出せや お宝 トパトパ トパパ
Sell off the treasure, topatopa topapa
買ってもチューキ行為 承認行為
Even if you buy it, it's approval behavior
なんてね ドロドロ欲望 暴き出され ペラペラ本音 見出され 正気と狂気 交錯行為
Just kidding! Muddy desires exposed, thin excuses revealed, sanity and madness intertwined!
グルグル世界が回らされて
The world spins round and round
スパチャリングな夜はハンマー
A super-chatting night, bring down the hammer
いざ Hammeraaaaan! Congratulations!
Here comes the Hammeraaaaan! Congratulations!
円 ドル ポンド ユーロ Money しゅきしゅき！ Ah!
Yen, dollar, pound, euro, money, love it, love it! Ah!
ルピア リラ ウォン 元 ドン！ Money Money Money！ はい！
Rupiah, lira, won, yuan, dong! Money, money, money! Yes!
どれがベストっちゃ？ レアル マルク クローネ ユーロ 海外の船 金銀銅
Which is best? Real, mark, krone, euro! Foreign ships, gold, silver, bronze!
お宝売って 新船買って お船に乗って ハッピー！ 出航して 嵐に遭って バッドエンド？
Sell treasure, buy a new ship, board the ship, happy! Set sail, hit a storm, bad end?
南太平洋で鉱山発見 アートな金貨掘り出しちゃって 大発見！ これをマリンと命名する！
Discovered a mine in the South Pacific, dug up artistic gold coins, major discovery! Naming it Marine!
愛の地球！
Earth of love!
船長の服！
Captain's clothes!
破れたスカーフ！
Torn scarf!
まだ足りない！
Still not enough!
脱ぎ捨てブーツ サービスサービス 我がままポッキーの要求！
Discarded boots, fan service service, selfish Pocky demand!
How much? (はい！100万円！)
How much? (Yes! 1 million yen!)
からの？ (はい！1億円！)
And then? (Yes! 100 million yen!)
からの？ (はい！1兆円！)
And then? (Yes! 1 trillion yen!)
増した声 How much?
A louder voice, How much?
(はい！1千兆！) からの？
(Yes! 1 quadrillion!) And then?
(はい！2千兆！) からの？
(Yes! 2 quadrillion!) And then?
(はい！3千兆！) ぶっ飛んで？
(Yes! 3 quadrillion!) Go crazy?
(5千兆！)
(5 quadrillion!)
ドキドキして rouge？
Heart-pounding rouge?
幕張、行きますよ～！
Makuhari, here we go~!
ねえ、言ったよね？ 年齢なんて関係ないってさ
Hey, didn't you say? That age doesn't matter at all
そういう面倒くさいのも含めて愛してくれるって
And that you'd love me including all that troublesome stuff
ねえねえ、言ったよね？ 言ってない？ ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ
Hey hey, didn't you say? You didn't? Hmm, is that how it is?
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
By the way, on this ship, the "Beautiful Girl Innocent" rule applies, you know?
まかせて！ 魔法で若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenated by magic
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ トクベツですよ～？
My secret true face is just for you, is that special enough~?
ah… アタシ厄介よ
Ah... I'm a handful
ah… 港なんかじゃ はしゃげないわ近頃はね
Ah... No port can excite me lately, you know?
宝の島にしてほしい気分 (出航ー！！)
I'm in the mood to make it a treasure island (Set sail!!)
キュートは正義 美少女無罪 キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Cute is justice, beautiful girl is innocent, aiming to be your number one, full speed ahead!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう (ahoy！！)
Honestly I'm not confident, but I'll do my best (Ahoy!!)
きゅっきゅっきゅるん きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん 恋する気持ち17歳
Kyu kyu kyurun, kyu kyu kyurunrun, feelings of love at 17 years old
0時になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
It becomes midnight, adult time
ド・キ・ド・キして rouge？
Heart-pounding rouge?
あぁ、お許しくだた～い！ このマリンの…… 魅力！ 魔力！ 不可抗力！ ──"罪な女"ね？
Ah~ Please forgive me~! This Marine's... Charm! Magic! Irresistible force! ──A "sinful woman", huh?
離さないでつかまっていて 世界の広さ見せかけたげるから！ (出航ー！！)
Don't let go, hold on tight, I'll show you how big the world is! (Set sail!!)
キュートは正義 美少女無罪 キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Cute is justice, beautiful girl is innocent, aiming to be your number one, full speed ahead!
冗談も大好きだけど真剣よ (ahoy！！)
I love jokes too, but I'm serious (Ahoy!!)
きゅっきゅっきゅるん きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん 恋する気持ち17歳
Kyu kyu kyurun, kyu kyu kyurunrun, feelings of love at 17 years old
0時になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
It becomes midnight, adult time
ド・キ・ド・キして rouge？ まだ早い♡
Heart-pounding rouge? Not yet ♡
“マリン”じゃなくて “マリン船長”だろぉん！？
Not "Marine", it's "Captain Marine", right!?
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らデン
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
紙飛行機の花びらを ある人は美しいと呟いた
"A paper airplane's petals..." Someone whispered they were beautiful.
この地球の横顔は どう見えてる？君の世界では
How does the profile of this Earth look in your world?
現実を逆さにして 無くしそうなものだけ振り落とした
Turning reality upside down, shaking off only what's about to be lost.
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら 指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
When I tried to pick them up in my palms, they slipped through my fingers and disappeared.
形あるものだけが全てじゃないけど
Physical things aren't everything, but...
形あるものが遠のいても欲しいよ
Even if physical things drift away, I still want them.
この世界を変えることは きっとできないけど
We probably can't change this world,
君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
but we should be able to change the world inside of you.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて 何一つ欠かせないから
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, withering—not a single moment can be missed,
最後に君が笑ってくれれば もうそれだけでいい
so if you smile in the end, that's all that matters.
言葉のない音紡ぐ人 優しさを編む人 それぞれの正義を分かってあげたい
Those weaving wordless sounds, those knitting kindness—I want to understand each of their justice.
絡まった矛盾と辻褄合わせ そんな切なさ抱え今日を生きて
Dealing with tangled contradictions and forcing logic, living today carrying such heartbreak,
分け合った灯り 隣から隣へ やがて一つに
the shared lights pass from neighbor to neighbor, eventually becoming one.
夜の帳へ息を吹き込んだ 君とじゃなきゃダメなんだ
Breathing life into the veil of night, it has to be with you.
このまま寝てしまうには 勿体ないほど
It's almost too wasteful to just fall asleep like this,
優しさに包まれた夜だった
it was a night wrapped in kindness.
はっきり浮かび上がった夢の輪郭は 確かに愛だった
The clearly outlined silhouette of the dream was undoubtedly love.
月が見守る今夜 そっと一瞬を抱きしめた 煌めく星
Watched over by the moon tonight, I gently embraced the moment under sparkling stars.
色や形 温度や響き 全て違っても 僕らは
Even if our colors, shapes, temperatures, and sounds are all different, we...
きっと最後には この音で繋がって
...will surely connect through this sound in the end.
この世界を変えることは
Changing this world...
きっとできないけど 君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
...is probably impossible, but we should be able to change the world inside of you.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて 何一つ欠かせないから
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, withering—not a single moment can be missed,
最後に君が笑ってくれれば もうそれだけでいい
so if you smile in the end, that's all that matters.
みんな聞いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for listening!
楽しんでくれましたか？
Did you all enjoy it?
STAGE4、まだまだ続きます！
Stage 4 is still going strong!
盛り上がっていってね！
Keep getting hyped!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
ただいまー！
We're back!
Stage4、始まりましたー！
Stage 4 has officially begun!
イエーイ！
Yay!
EXPOとフェス最終日だよ！まだまだいけるよねー！
It's the final day of EXPO and Fes! You've still got energy left, right?!
ちょっとね、今歌って踊ったばかりで疲れて…ないです！
Having just sung and danced, I'm a bit tired... Not at all!
まだまだ元気バリバリありまーす！
We still have tons of energy left!
すごい元気だねー
You're so energetic!
でもこんなにもさ、たくさんの声援を浴びたらさ、パワーもらえちゃうよねー！
But getting so many cheers from everyone gives us so much power!
ほんとにさー！
It really does!
でもまだまだね、ステージは続いていきますのでみなさん
But the stage is still going to continue, so everyone...
右肩上がりで…もっとでかい声で！
...keep building momentum... with even louder voices!
楽しかったねー！
That was so much fun!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ちょっと自己紹介からさせてもらいます！
First, let us introduce ourselves!
可愛いポジティブ...
Cute, positive...
ジーニアス！
Genius!
めっちゃ嬉しい！ホロライブDEV_G ReGLOSSの一条莉々華だよ！コンリリー！
I'm so happy! I'm Ichijou Ririka from Hololive DEV_G ReGLOSS! Konriri!
コンリリー！
Konriri!
いやーめっちゃ嬉しい！そして！
Yay, I'm so happy! And next!
はい！ホロライブDEV_G ReGLOSS音乃瀬奏でーす！
Hi! I'm Otonose Kanade from Hololive DEV_G ReGLOSS!
え何何何！？
Wait, what, what, what?
さっきまでさ、「ちょっとドキドキする」とか言ってたのに！ちゃんと喋れてる！頑張れ！
Just a moment ago, you were saying "I'm a bit nervous"! But you're talking so well! Good job!
皆さん楽しんでますかー？
Is everyone having fun?
ペンライトも莉々奏カラーにしてくれてる！
You even set your penlights to Riri-Kana colors!
ねーすごい！ありがとー！
Wow, that's amazing! Thank you!
はい！ということで、
Alright, so!
もうすでに何曲かみんなにお披露目できたと思うんですけれど、
We've already performed a few songs for you today,
今回ちょっとね、5th Fesのテーマとして「Ridin' on Dreams」ということで、
but for this 5th Fes theme "Ridin' on Dreams",
ステージと皆さんの掛け橋の形がトロッコとして出てきました！
trolleys shaped as bridges between the stage and the audience appeared!
すごかったよねー！
That was amazing!
奏と私達も乗らせてもらったんですけど、
Kanade and I got to ride on them too,
もう本当にみんなのね、笑顔が嬉しそうな顔が見えました！
and we could really see all of your happy, smiling faces!
見えてたよー！顔とか持ってるグッズとかー！
We saw you! Your faces and the merch you were holding!
最高ー！
Awesome!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
もうね、せっかくMCを務めさせていただいたから、
Since we have this chance to host the MC segment,
なんかやりたいことあるんじゃないのー？
isn't there something you want to do?
あれー！？
Huh!?
社長何やりたい？
President, what do you want to do?
いやもう一番最初の全体曲のときから、
Ever since the very first group song,
みんなの掛け声とかペンライトとかがもうブワーって！
everyone's cheers and penlights were coming at us like whoosh!
ブワーって嬉しすぎるくらい来て、
Coming at us so intensely, it made me so happy,
ちょっとそれをこのMC中にもやりたいんですけど、いいですかー？
so I want to try that during this MC segment too. Is that okay?
いいですかー？
Is that okay?
やったー！
Yay!
じゃあ莉々華はペンライトを使ってちょっとみんなと交流したいです！
Then Ririka wants to interact with everyone using penlights!
いいですか？皆さんペンライトの準備はー？
Is that okay? Everyone, prepare your penlights!
社長の色分かってねー！
Make sure you know President's color!
じゃあ...
Then...
ちょっと全部を濃いピンク！薄いピンクじゃないですよ！莉々華の濃いピンクにしてみて貰ってもいいですかー？
Could you change them all to deep pink? Not light pink! Ririka's deep pink, please!
もう出来てるー！
They're already pink!
すごーい！よかったね！
Amazing! That's awesome!
お花畑みたーい！
It looks like a flower garden!
じゃあ次は奏のカラーである黄色にしてもらってもいいですかー？
Then next, could you change them to Kanade's color, yellow?
奏の色もしてくれるのー？
You'll do Kanade's color too?
ありがとー！最高！
Thank you! Awesome!
じゃあ次は莉々華が「ピンク」って言ったらピンク、「黄色」って言ったら黄色にしてね！
Next, when Ririka says "pink", change to pink, and when I say "yellow", change to yellow!
できるかなー？
Can you do it?
時差あるんじゃないのー？
Won't there be a delay?
あ、ピンクになってるー！
Ah, it's turning pink!
すごーい！あ、カチカチ換えてるカチカチ換えてる！
Amazing! Ah, they're clicking to change them!
変わってるー！
It's changing!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
じゃあ好きな色ー！
Now, pick your favorite color!
ねーすごい！お花畑みたい！
Wow, amazing! Like a flower field!
ありがとうございます！とっても嬉しいです！
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
じゃあ奏は何やりたい？
So what do you want to do, Kanade?
奏はもう分かってると思うけどー、
I think you all already know...
奏がちょっとこのDay 2のMCとして出たということは... 今日はないよー！じゃないんだなー！
Since Kanade appeared as Day 2's MC host... it doesn't mean "not today"!
みんな知ってるよね！奏が「明日はー？」って言ったら皆さんも生まれてきて一番のでっかい声で「月曜日ー！」って叫んでくださいね！いいですかー？
Everyone knows, right? When Kanade says "Tomorrow is...?", yell "Monday!" with the loudest voice of your life! Is that okay?
いいよー！月曜日ですよー！いきますよー！
Sure! It's Monday! Here we go!
明日はー？
Tomorrow is...?
月曜日ー！
Monday!
最高ー！ありがとー！
Awesome! Thank you!
いや、でも明日が月曜日でもね、そんな疲れを吹っ飛ばすくらい、今日は最高のパフォーマンスをね、みんなに届けていきますので、皆さんまだまだ...
Even if tomorrow is Monday, we'll deliver such a fantastic performance today that it'll blow away all your tiredness, so everyone...
盛り上がっていきますよー！
Let's get hyped up!
いいね！
Awesome!
もっといけるねー！
We can go even further!
まだまだいけるねー！
We can still keep going!
最高！
Awesome!
はい！ということで...
Alright, so...
あのね、今回現地に来てくださっているみんなと
So, everyone who came to the venue today...
配信で見てくださっているみんなも
...and everyone watching on the livestream...
そう、コメントも見えてますからね！
...yes, we can see your comments too!
配信のみんなは、ハッシュタグ
Everyone on stream, please use the hashtag...
#ホロライブフェスEXPO26Day3 と
#hololivefesEXPO26Day3...
たくさんポストしてくれたら嬉しいです！
...and post a lot, we'd be so happy!
いいねー！
Awesome!
探してそして、楽しいお知らせがあるんですけど...
And also, we have an exciting announcement...
楽しいお知らせ？なにー？
An exciting announcement? What is it?
YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方は、ここまでー！
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is the end!
悲しいよー！
That's so sad!
はい、でもね、よかったら皆さんまだまだ楽しいライブは続きますので
But if you'd like, the fun concert will still continue...
引き続き見てもらえたら嬉しいです！
...so we'd be happy if you keep watching!
いっぱい声出して応援してね！
Cheer loud and support us!
応援してください！
Please support us!
それではですね、ちょっと次の曲に入りたいと思いますので
Now then, we're going to move on to the next song...
せーのって言ったら、みんなで今回のテーマである「Ridin' on Dreams」と叫んでもらえたら嬉しいです！
...so when we say "Ready, set...", we'd love it if everyone shouts this event's theme, "Ridin' on Dreams"!
いいですかー？
Are you ready?
オーケー！
Okay!
それじゃあいくよ！
Alright, here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
Ridin' on Dreams!
引き続き楽しんでねー！
Enjoy the rest of the show!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!